What now?
How can I escape
the bullying?
This is hopeless
And I can't believe
I'm sitting
with Kim Hyeong-ju
Am I an idiot or what?
I shouldn't have
done that
Right, I'll pretend
like I'm asleep
That's
the best strategy
They won't bother me
as much
I'm sure
they won't wake me up
What the heck?
Did I actually
fall asleep?
We're not there yet
But why is it so cramped?
What the hell?
This isn't like him
Why is he
suddenly acting nice?
What's going on?
Ever since
the school trip
Hyeon-wu is sending
weird signs
What the hell?
It's so creepy
Il-tak, my favorite doll
Get over here
Just ignore them
What?
He's never stood up
for me like this
Hong Il-tak
Didn't I tell you
to get over here?
Are you crazy?
Just a second
Hey!
Listen up
I'll kill anyone
who bothers
Hong Il-tak from now on
So, stop it
Especially you
Kim Hyeong-ju
You got a problem
with that?